tunefab.com 2018-07-16

# Privacy Policy | TuneFab

**Effective Date: May 25, 2018**

TuneFab Software Inc. ("us", "we", or "our") fully understands the importance of protecting personal information and is committed to safeguarding your privacy. This Privacy Policy Statement covers the collection, use, disclosure, control and security of your personal information that may be collected by TuneFab. It has been updated as required by European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). By accessing our website (www.tunefab.com) or purchasing our desktop applications (the "Products", "Services"), you agree to this Privacy Statement in addition to any other agreements we might have with you. 

So, please take a moment to read the following to make sure that you are aware of our latest privacy practices. Your privacy is a priority at TuneFab, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

Collection of Your Personal Information

While using our Products or accessing our website, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information ("Personal Data") that can be used to contact or identify you. 

Here are some of the situations in which you may need to provide personal information to us:  
1\. Contact us for help or any other reasons;  
2\. Visit our website (www.tunefab.com);  
3\. Register as an end-user of our Products and Services and an account is created for you;  
4\. Error reports or application analytic data that have been sent by the website.

The type of information we collect will depend on your interaction with TuneFab. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:1\. Contact Information: Full name, email address, phone number, zip code, country, province, city, and similar contact info;  
2\. Payment Information: All payment information like credit card number, billing address and other info you submit are collected and used by our payment processor in accordance with their privacy policies. But we won’t collect or store your payment info on our server;  
3\. Usage Data: We may also collect information about how TuneFab website is accessed and used (Usage Data”). It may include information like IP address, browser type, browser version, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other diagnostic data;  
4\. User Communications: Your full name, email address, mailing address, a phone number will be required when you contact us for support, participate in our surveys or respond to our email campaigns about upgrades, new products, promotions or special offers;  
5\. Cookies: We use cookies to store user preference which is nothing to do with the personal information in order to help us improve service quality. So, when you access our website, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters to your computer. It can let the web page server identify the site that you are viewing.

Use of Your Personal Information

TuneFab may use the information that we collect about you to:

Deliver services such as newsletters or products that you request or purchased;

Solve your tech questions or recover your license code;

Send you service-related information, such as confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, special offers, and other new services from TuneFab, if you required;

To analyze and improve our software program;

Understand you and your preferences to enhance your experience. 

Disclosure of Your Personal Information to Third Parties

TuneFab will work its best to keep your personal information confidential and secure. Once we collected your personal information, we will not share this information with any others without your permission, except for the limited exceptions already listed. They will only be used for the purposes stated above. And we will never sell your personal data. 

In the following circumstances, TuneFab may share your information with third parties, for examples: 

We may share your personal information when we have your consent; 

We provide personal information to trusted partners like vendors, credit card processor and those assist us in operating our website, conducting our business or providing Services to you, as long as these third parties agree to keep this information confidential in accomplice with European Union's General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR");

We will disclose your personal information if it is required by legal requirements, government officials, or other third parties pursuant to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process or requirement applicable to us;

We may share your information to other third parties with your consent or direction to do so.

Security of Your Personal Information

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

Children's Privacy

TuneFab does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children"). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

Links to Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Changes to This Privacy Policy

Occasionally, we may change this privacy policy for some purpose. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice like email notification. But we still encourage you to periodically review the TuneFab Privacy Policy for the latest information on our privacy practices.

Contact Information

Please send any questions or comments on our privacy practices to [support@tunefab.com](mailto:support@tunefab.com).
